No puedo creer que esté firmando
the contract with my own
father.
So...
Thank you.
They cut off your allowance, huh?
They took
everything.
And I don't even remember
anything from that night.
Do you know who that man was?
You ordered him.
I'm afraid not.
You know, I just paid for
the service and
they promised me
the most handsome man.
What am I gonna do?
I don't even know where to start.
I never worked a day in my life.
Oh, I know, I know, I know.
Our office is looking for
a secretary.
You should apply.
Oh, and the boss is
gorgeous - like,
out-of-this-world hot.
Is he that toxic suit?
Oh, stop it.
Any girl will do anything
to spend a night with him.
When's the interview?